Muhamad Wildan Nugraha

Bogor, Indonesia | 081294875992 | wildan.wildan1212@gmail.com

INTRODUCTION

I am a 24 years old frontend developer website & mobile that have more than with 2 years experienced in digital banking industry who has a high passion and enthusiasm for the world of all fields related to software development, with severalabilities that I have,namely very understanding of HTML and CSS (able to change design into code), javascript, Typescript, several frameworks such as React Js, Redux toolkit,Redux Ioniq, React Native, Next Js, Tailwind CSS then for native android development I'm used to using kotlin.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Amar bank - WFO, Jakarta

Frontend Engineer

February 2022 - Current

at Amar Bank my role as a front-end engineer who has the responsibility to help develop and maintain several websites from Amar Bank digital banking App & amar bank embedded banking, mostly using React & Next JS Framework for web also for mobile Android Native i using Kotlin.

Jobdesk:

Development embedded banking web app & ios webview Amar Bank (registration,transfer, direct debit, mutation) features using Next JS Framework.

- Make code coverage unit test above 20% using RTL & jest in every feature.
- · Make E2E test using cypress for every features.

Refactor company profile & support website Amar Bank retail Banking to Next JSFramework.

Development CRM Amar Bank retail Banking & Amar Bank MSME website using Next JS.

Development CMS Amar Bank as a fullstack using MERN stack (Mongo DB, Express, React, Node).

Development Amar Bank Android Digital Banking app using Kotlin & Android Studio.

Weekend Inc - Remote, WFH

Frontend Developer

October 2021 - Desember 2021

Jobdesk:

My job is to help convert & slicing design to react component, also I collaboration with UI/UX Designer and Backend Developer to development e-commerce website using React & Typescript.

PT. Astrajingga Inovasi Digital – Remote, WFH

Web Developer Intern

March 2021 - May 2021

Jobdesk:

My job is to help design UI & Slicing design to react component, also I support the senior developer to fixwebsite bug issues on the client side (frontend) using React & javascript.

Gunadarma University Electronics & Computer Laboratory - Depok, Indonesia

ELECTRONICS & COMPUTER LABORATORY ASSISTANT

September 2018 - April 2021

Jobdesk:

During my time as a laboratory assistant, I had a jobdesk as the person in charge of the Embedded System practicum where my job was to conduct research and update on the embedded systems practicum learning module and make prototypes of the embedded systems practicum project.

EDUCATION

Gunadarma University - Depok, Indonesia

2017 - 2021

Bachelor of Computer Science (B.Sc),

GPA: 3.40 / 4.00

SKILLS

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Typescript, React, Next JS, Redux, React Native, SCSS/SASS, Jquery, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Figma, Bitbucket, Git, Circle CI, Mongo DB, Firebase, Cypress, Jest, React Testing Library, Kotlin, Android Studio.

LANGUAGE

English (Upper Intermediate) with EFSet Score English Test 60 (B2)

CERTIFICATION & TRAINING

- Training Intro to Full Stack Developer Program Fresh Graduate Academy Digital Talent Scholarship(by the Ministry of Communication and Information of the Republic of Indonesia).
- IDCamp Front end Developer Path (by Indosat Ooredoo and Dicodi Academy).
- Database Administration Fundamentals (by Microsoft Technology Associate).
- Web Development Path(Node.js) (by Progate).

WORKING PROJECT

Amar Bank Transfer Website Application

Created to be one of the features in Amar Bank embedded banking product. using React JS , SASS, Redux, Axios.

Amar Bank Embedded Banking Registration Website Application

Created for user can doing registration amar bank account. Using React JS, SASS, Redux, Axios.

Amar Bank Direct Debit Website Application

Created to be one of feature in Amar bank embedded banking product that has functionality doing some payment using amar bank account in embedded banking. using Next js, SASS, Axios.

Amar Bank Embedded Widget Website Application

Created to be entry point where user can using Amar Bank embedded banking features. using NextJS, SASS, Axios.

- Amar Bank Digital Banking & SMB Business CRM Platform Website
 Created for handle & store all amar bank customer data. using React TS, SASS, Redux.
- CMS Amar Bank Retail Banking Website
 Created for handle some content in Amar bank company profile website. using React JS, SASS,MongoDB, Express js.
- Amar Bank Digital Banking Android App
 Digital banking app from Amar Bank. using Kotlin & Android Studio.